Finding aid to the Mary Daly papers SSC.MS.00637
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES II. Writings, 1973-2004; 30.376 linear feet (38 containers)
  - Woman's Press Miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 30)
  - Women's Press Andree's Book (Box 30)
  - Pure Lust Frauenoffensive, 1984 (Box 30)
  - Beyond God the Father Dutch Publisher, 1993 (Box 30)
  - Most Recent Molly Sherdan, 1992-1993 (Box 30)
  - Legal Case Radio Pacifica, 1992-1993 (Box 30)
  - The Happy Cunt, 1994-1995 (Box 30)
  - Outercourse Publicity Packet, 1993 (Box 30)
  - Oshkosh, WI, 2007 (Box 30)
  - Speaking Engagements, 1994-1995 (Box 30)
  - Sue Banner Speaking, 2001 (Box 30)
  - Interface, 1996 (Box 30)
  - Speaking Engagements, 2001 (Box 30)
  - Defense Fund, 1999 (Box 30)
  - Pacific University Oregon, 2002 (Box 30)
  - Speaking Invitations, 1998 (Box 31)
  - Agnes Scott College, 2002 (Box 31)
  - US California, 2002 (Box 31)
  - Speaking Event- Athens OH, 2001 (Box 31)
  - Monmouth College, 2002 (Box 31)
  - Re-Imagining in Minneapolis, 2000 (Box 31)
  - Florida State, 2001 (Box 31)
  - Speaking Invitations, 2001 (Box 31)
  - Ohio- Speaking, 2001 (Box 31)
  - Utah, 2001 (Box 31)
  - Speaking, 2000 (Box 31)
  - Germany Speech, 2000 (Box 31)
  - Switzerland, 1999 (Box 31)
  - Lecture Krystyna Colburn, 2000-2001 (Box 31)
  - Speaking, 1993-1998 (Box 31)
  - CIA- Contemporary Issues Agency, 1999 (Box 31)
  - Europe Trip, 1994 (Box 31)
  - International Association for Women Philosophers, 1998 (Box 31)
  - Speaking, 1993 (Box 31)
  - Speaking Engagements, 2000-2001 (Box 31)
  - Speaking Lectures, 1992 (Box 31)
  - Gyn/Ecology drafts (Box 31)
  - New Yorker- Courage to Sun, 1995-1996 (Box 31)
  - Alice Quinn and David Kuhn, 1996 (Box 31)
  - New Yorker Article, 1995 (Box 31)
  - New Yorker Business, 1995 (Box 31)
  - Women's Press Publicity Tour, 1993 (Box 31)
  - Speaking Engagements, 1985-1987 (Box 32)
  - Lilly Friedberg, 1987-1988 (Box 32)
  - The Church and the Second Sex Contract, 1984 (Box 32)
  - Beyond God the Father Draft, 1974 (Box 32)
  - Be-Dazzling (Box 32)
  - Outercourse 4th Spiral Galaxy, 1989-1990 (Box 32)
  - Nancy Kelly (Box 32)
  - Beacon and Other Permissions, 1991-1992 (Box 32)
  - Beacon Catalog, 1991 (Box 32)
  - Wickedary Wendy Strothman, 1990-1992 (Box 32)
  - Women's Press, 1991 (Box 32)
  - Gyn/Ecology Reviews, 1978-1980 (Box 32)
  - Loose in Box, 1992 (Box 32)
  - Press, 1978-1979 (Box 32)
  - Contracts and Publishing, 1989-1992 (Box 32)
  - Amazon Grace, 2005 (Box 32)
  - Polity Press, 1989 (Box 33)
  - Women of Power, 1990 (Box 33)
  - Ms Magazine, 1989 (Box 33)
  - Permissions, 1989-1990 (Box 33)
  - Beacon- Gail Bryan photograph, 1981-2003 (Box 33)
  - Quintessence Jill Kneerim, 1996-2000 (Box 33)
  - Permissions for "Q Leap", 2004 (Box 33)
  - Foreign Rights Publishers, 1982-1983 (Box 33)
  - Dentist- Howard Levine, 2004 (Box 33)
  - Notes (Box 33)
  - Amazon Grace Proposal Recovery (Box 33)
  - Amazon Grace Drafts (Box 33)
  - Heaven's Gate, 1998-2000 (Box 33)
  - Jacket Copy- Palgrave, 2005 (Box 33)
  - Amazon Grace Articles, 1993-2004 (Box 33)
  - Oshkosh Speech, 2002 (Box 33)
  - Amazon Grace Outline of Chapters (Box 33)
  - Amazon Grace Drafts (Box 33)
  - Amazon Grace Notes, 2004 (Box 33)
  - Leo Strauss, 2003 (Box 33)
  - Josie- Publisher, 2001 (Box 33)
  - Marija Gimbutas, 2003 (Box 33)
  - Amazon Grace Illustration, 2005 (Box 33)
  - Beacon Press Royalties, 1980-2005 (Box 33)
  - Future Speaking Engagements, 2004-2007 (Box 33)
  - Speaking- Miscellaneous, 2003-2006 (Box 33)
  - Boston Globe Article, 2006 (Box 33)
  - Amazon Grace (Box 33)
  - Outercourse Drafts, 1992 (Box 33, Box 34)
  - Amazon Garce, 2005 (Box 34)
  - Copyright Clearing House, 2007 (Box 34)
  - Reviews, 1964-1993 (Box 34)
  - Amazon Grace, 2005 (Box 34)
  - Word Count, 1997 (Box 34)
  - Endnote of All Chapters, 1996 (Box 34)
  - Quintessence Drafts (Box 35)
  - Quintessence Research, 1994-1997 (Box 35)
  - Quintessence Letters from Diane Piedmont, 1995 (Box 35)
  - Tina Brown, 1996 (Box 35)
  - Murdered Au Pair in Boston, 1996 (Box 35)
  - Quintessence Research Notes (Box 35)
  - Outercourse Draft (Box 36)
  - Statement of Support from Membership of American Academy of Religion (Box 36)
  - Important! Contains Magical Chart (Box 36)
  - Pure Lust, 1984 (Box 36)
  - Wickedary and Outercourse (Box 36)
  - Quintessence Drafts and Proofs, 1998 (Box 37, Box 38)
  - Amazon Grace Drafts, 2003-2004 (Box 38)
  - Amazon Grace Notes, 2001 (Box 38)
  - Amazon Grace Proposal, 2004 (Box 38)
  - Indexes, 1998 (Box 38)
  - Quintessence Publicity Beacon (Box 38)
  - Quintessence Paperback from Beacon Press, 1999 (Box 38)
  - Italy, 1999-2003 (Box 38)
  - Luciana Percovich, 2001-2002 (Box 38)
  - Lucia Birnbaum, 2002-2003 (Box 38)
  - Quintessence Book Proposal, 2003 (Box 38)
  - Quintessence Reviews, 1999-2000 (Box 38)
  - Norton Publishers, 1988 (Box 38)
  - Beacon Press Sales, 2004 (Box 38)
  - Gyn/Ecology Book Jacket (Box 38)
  - "The Qualitative Leap Beyond Patriarchal Religion", 2002 (Box 38)
  - Published Article, Press, Miscellaneous, 1999-2001 (Box 38)
  - Amazon Grace, 2001-2004 (Box 38)
  - Quintessence Helene Atwan, 1998 (Box 38)
  - Quintessence "Wanderground" Preface, 1997 (Box 38)
  - Frauenoffensive Royal, 1997 (Box 38)
  - Women's Press Permissions, 1997 (Box 38)
  - London, John and Steve Moore, 1991-1996 (Box 38)
  - Quintessence Notes, 1980-1995 (Box 38)
  - Amazon Grace, 1999-2001 (Box 38)
  - Amazon Grace Palgrave, 2005 (Box 38)
  - Publications, 1958-1968 (Box 39)
  - Quintessence Old Versions Drafts and Comments, 1995-1998 (Box 39)
  - Re: "Commonweal" Abortion Article, 1972 (Box 39)
  - Travel and Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1999-2008 (Box 39)
  - Clippings TCSS, 1968-1973 (Box 39)
  - Harvard Seminar, 1971 (Box 39)
  - Works in Journals, 1971-1972 (Box 39)
  - Religious Journals, 1969-1975 (Box 39)
  - Wickedary Speech, 1986 (Box 39)
  - The Click Anthology- "Why I Became a Feminist, 1994-1995 (Box 39)
  - Something to Savor "Oh... Fudge", 1996 (Box 39)
  - Women's Press, 1997-1998 (Box 39)
  - Wee Girls, 1996 (Box 39)
  - Gale Research Autobiography, 1997 (Box 39)
  - Wickedary (Box 40)
  - Publications- Ms Magazine, 1974-1975 (Box 40)
  - Publications- Reuters Book, 1973-1974 (Box 40)
  - Second Internation Symposium of Belief, 1975 (Box 40)
  - Publications, 1975-1984 (Box 40)
  - Publishers, 1967-1973 (Box 40)
  - Rockefeller Grant Publicity List, 1975-1976 (Box 40)
  - Beyond God the Father Clippings, 1973 (Box 40)
  - Beyond God the Father Adoptions, 1979 (Box 40)
  - Beyond God the Father Corrections, 1973 (Box 40)
  - Beacon Press Distribution, 1973-1977 (Box 40)
  - Wells Drorbaugh, 1977 (Box 40)
  - Beacon Press Excerpts, 1973-1981 (Box 40)
  - Gyn/Ecology Excerpts First Serial of Publications, 1978-1979 (Box 40)
  - Beyond God the Father Reviews, 1973-1975 (Box 40)
  - Beyond God the Father French, 1975-1976 (Box 40)
  - Foreign Rights, 1975-1976 (Box 40)
  - Beacon Press, 1973-1979 (Box 40)
  - Beacon Letter of Protest (Box 40)
  - Beacon Press- Beyond God the Father Mass Market, 1976 (Box 40)
  - Beacon Press- Paperbacks, 1974 (Box 40)
  - Beyond God the Father Paperback, 1974-1976 (Box 40)
  - Beyond God the Father Expenses, 1973 (Box 40)
  - Beyond God the Father British Edition, 1975-1977 (Box 40)
  - Beyond God the Father Publication Party, 1973 (Box 40)
  - The Church and the Second Sex Reviews, 1975 (Box 40)
  - Church and the Second Sex Introduction (Box 40)
  - GMO Article, 1999 (Box 40)
  - Amazon Grace Greenpeace, 2000 (Box 40)
  - NRDC Humane Farming, 2001 (Box 40)
  - PETA- Testing/National Anti-vivisection, 2000-2001 (Box 40)
  - Papers Loose in Box, 2001-2002 (Box 40)
  - Miscellaneous Pam Interview, 2003 (Box 40)
  - Neoconservatives, 2003 (Box 40)
  - Amazon Grace Articles, 2000-2001 (Box 40)
  - Toxins in Environment, 2003 (Box 40)
  - Amazon Grace Mad Cow Disease, 2001 (Box 40)
  - Animals, 1999 (Box 40)
  - Robots Genetic Engineering- Cloning, 1998 (Box 40)
  - Amazon Grace Text and Notes (Box 40)
  - Prisons and Slave Labor, 2001 (Box 40)
  - Hunting- Texas Baby, 2001 (Box 40)
  - Right Wing Information PRA, 2001 (Box 40)
  - GE Food, 2000 (Box 40)
  - Animals and Religions (Box 40)
  - Global Warming, AIDS, Nanotechnology, 2000 (Box 41)
  - Cloning, 2001 (Box 41)
  - "The Strategy for Electricity is Democracy" article, 2001 (Box 41)
  - Bio-engineering Media World Watch, 1999-2000 (Box 41)
  - Bush and Government Assassination, 2001 (Box 41)
  - Gene Patenting, 2001 (Box 41)
  - Gene Watch, 1999-2001 (Box 41)
  - Stem Cell Research, 2001 (Box 41)
  - Lawsuit Against Jesuits, 2002 (Box 41)
  - ETC- Erosion, Tech, etc, 1999-2001 (Box 41)
  - Miscellaneous News Clippings, 2001-2002 (Box 41)
  - Homeopathy, 2002 (Box 41)
  - CFIDS, 2000 (Box 41)
  - Rainforest (Box 41)
  - Amazon Grace Age, 2001 (Box 41)
  - Grey2K USA, 2000-2001 (Box 41)
  - "Soul Loss" by Linda Hogan, 1999 (Box 41)
  - Jeanette Normandin, 2001 (Box 41)
  - GM Animals/Farmaceuticals, 2001 (Box 41)
  - Drug Industry- Bioterrorism, 2001 (Box 41)
  - Speaking Engagements, 2004-2006 (Box 41)
  - Mormons, 2001 (Box 41)
  - GAIA, 1992 (Box 41)
  - Afghan Women Swatch Feminism, 2001 (Box 41)
  - Cloning, 2001 (Box 41)
  - Turning Point Project, 2002 (Box 41)
  - Miscellaneous- To Be Checked, 2000 (Box 41)
  - Flyers, 2002-2006 (Box 41)
  - Gage Foundation (Box 41)
  - Papers Loose in Box, 2004 (Box 41)
  - Drew University, 2006 (Box 41)
  - "Mutual Pun-ishment?" (Box 41)
  - Luciana Speech, 2003 (Box 41)
  - Amy Goodman Democracy Now, 2006 (Box 41)
  - Amazon Grace Publicity (Box 41)
  - Italian, 1987-1990 (Box 41)
  - Speaking Engagements, 1976 (Box 41)
  - Beyond God the Father Italian, 1990 (Box 41)
  - Augsburg Fortress Publishers, 2006 (Box 41)
  - Royalties, 1998 (Box 41)
  - Speaking Engagements, 2006 (Box 41)
  - Outercourse Gig Stuff (Box 41)
  - Second Galaxy, 1990 (Box 41)
  - Third Galaxy, 1990 (Box 41)
  - Spiral Galaxy (Box 41)
  - Old Chapter One (Box 41)
  - Prelude to First Spiral (Box 41)
  - Notes for Part Two Logbook (Box 41)
  - Sister Madeleva, 1964 (Box 41)
  - Outercourse Part One, 1988 (Box 41)
  - Fragmentation, 1988 (Box 41)
  - Nina Menkes, 1987-1989 (Box 41)
  - Materials for Feminist Allies, 1988 (Box 41)
  - Outercourse Notes and Outlines, 2003-2005 (Box 41)
  - Wickedary Carla R. Ellard (Box 41)
  - Amazon Grace Chapter 2, 2001 (Box 41)
  - Notes for Post-Outercourse, 2002 (Box 41)
  - Greenham Common, 1999-2000 (Box 41)
  - Arctic Wildlife Refuge, 2001 (Box 41)
  - Pornography Trafficking, 2001 (Box 41)
  - "Shame and Guilt by Judith Herman, 1997 (Box 41)
  - Bush as "Loner"- Ignores Europe's Opinion, 2001 (Box 41)
  - Women and AIDS, 2001 (Box 41)
  - Smallpox Vaccine, 2001-2002 (Box 41)
  - Sixth Dimension (Box 41)
  - Loose in Box, 2001 (Box 41)
  - Classes on Pornography, 2001 (Box 41)
  - Antidepressants, 2002 (Box 41)
  - Amazon Grace Biotech, 2001 (Box 41)
  - Ellie Smeal on Afghan Women, 2001 (Box 41)
  - Amazon Grace, 1998 (Box 41)
  - Philosophy Now, 2001 (Box 41)
  - "Qualitative Leaps", 1975 (Box 41)
  - Anna Chapters 1-4, 2002 (Box 41)
  - Proprioception, 2000-2001 (Box 41)
  - Cell Technology/Killing Fields, 2004 (Box 41)
  - Unidentified Papers (Box 41)
  - Amazon Grace Articles Science, 2001-2004 (Box 41)
  - Hurricane Katrina File, 2005 (Box 41)
  - Book Pages for Palgrave, 2004 (Box 41)
  - Beacon Press, 2005 (Box 41)
  - Alaska, 2002 (Box 41)
  - Vet Fem of America, 1997-1998 (Box 42)
  - Drought in US, 2001 (Box 42)
  - Laura Wilder, 2001 (Box 42)
  - Starhawk, 2001 (Box 42)
  - Feminism and Ecology, 2001 (Box 42)
  - GM Food, 2001 (Box 42)
  - Amazon Grace (Box 42)
  - Publications, 1968-1977 (Box 42)
  - Publications for Conferences and AAR, 1972-1977 (Box 42)
  - People Who Could Write Reviews for Amazon Grace, 2005-2006 (Box 42)
  - Copyright Clearing House- Royalties, 2006 (Box 42)
  - Amazon Grace Trivia, 2006 (Box 42)
  - Quintessence Proposal, Final (Box 42)
  - Quintessence General, 1995 (Box 42)
  - Women's Press, 2001 (Box 42)
  - Copyright Clearance Center, 1999 (Box 42)
  - Miscellaneous Writings, 2007 (Box 42)
  - Lise Clouter-Steele, 2001 (Box 42)
  - Amazon Grace Research (Box 42)
  - Amazon Grace Research and Notes, 2004 (Box 43)
  - Publications (Box 43)
  - Beacon Press/Promotions, 2001-2002 (Box 43)
  - Book Jackets, 2001 (Box 43)
  - Heights and Raymond for Chapter 12, 1979 (Box 43)
  - Amazon Grace Depleted Uranium, 2004 (Box 43)
  - Outercourse Manuscript, 1992 (Box 43)
  - Outercourse Manuscript Draft 2 (Box 43)
  - Outercourse Second Draft (Box 44)
  - Quintessence Chapter 4 and 5 draft, 1997-1998 (Box 44)
  - Quintessence Notes (Box 44)
  - Letter to Indexer, 1998 (Box 44)
  - Quintessence Drafts and Notes, 1995-1997 (Box 44)
  - Quintessence Correspondence, 1998 (Box 44)
  - Book Reviews, 1958 (Box 44)
  - "Antifeminism in the Church" (Box 44)
  - Amazon Grace Manuscript (Box 44)
  - Quintessence Drafts and Notes, 1995-1996 (Box 44)
  - The Church and the Second Sex Reviews, 1968-1970 (Box 44)
  - Amazon Grace Drafts and Notes (Box 44)
  - Computer Chips Replace Brain, 2001 (Box 44)
  - Amazon Grace Drafts and Notes (Box 44)
  - Books- Flyers New Words (Box 44)
  - Quintessence Flyers, 1998 (Box 45)
  - Amazon Grace Edits, 2005 (Box 45)
  - Barbara Flannagan/Palgrave, 2005 (Box 45)
  - Amazon Grace Footnotes (Box 45)
  - "Prelude to First Galaxy" (Box 45)
  - Publishers and Agents, 2003 (Box 45)
  - Personal/Professional/Publishing notes, correspondence and articles, 1998-2004 (Box 45)
  - Professional/Publishing correspondence and materials, 2003-2005 (Box 45)
  - Personal and Professional Publications, 2004-2007 (Box 45)
  - Unidentified Book Excerpts (Box 45)
  - Gyn/Ecology Permissions, 1982 (Box 45)
  - Jacket Copy, 2005 (Box 45)
  - Manuscript of Article on Maritain (Unpublished), 1966 (Box 45)
  - Notes and Bibliography to Unidentified Books (Box 45)
  - Hedge School Ideas and "Mutterings of a Crone" Ideas, 2007 (Box 45)
  - Articles on Mary Daly and Italian Quintessence, 1999-2002 (Box 45)
  - Articles, 1989 (Box 45)
  - Memorial Service, 2010 (Box 45)
  - Quintessence Chapter 5, 1997 (Box 45)
  - Quintessence Outlines (Box 45)
  - Quintessence Chapters 2 and 3, 1996 (Box 45)
  - Quintessence Canny Comments, 1997 (Box 45)
  - Quintessence Notes for Chapter 7 (Box 45)
  - Quintessence Chapters, 1995-1996 (Box 45)
  - Old Stuff, 1995 (Box 45)
  - Quintessence Munuscript, 1995-1997 (Box 45)
  - Amazon Grace Galleys (Box 45)
  - Amazon Grace Revies, 2005-2008 (Box 45)
  - Reviews, 1999 (Box 45)
  - Mary Daly Articles/Interviews/Lectures/Reviews of Books, 1971-2007 (Box 45)
  - Publishers' Info and Copyright Info, 2002-2008 (Box 45)
  - Copyright Clearance Center, 2004-2006 (Box 45)
  - Beyond God the Father, 2010 (Box 45)
  - Beacon Press, 2003-2008 (Box 45)
  - "What id Wrong with God? Everything" (Box 45)
  - "After the Death of God the Father", 1971 (Box 45)
  - Gyn/Ecology Reviews (Box 45)
  - Amazon Grace, 2001 (Box 45)
  - Amazon Grace digital files, 2000-2004; 4 items (4 floppy disks, 3.5 inch); 0.002 Gigabytes (7 files copied from 4 floppy disks) (Box 66)
    Proposal and drafts of relating to Amazon Grace
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    This content was received from the donor in digital form and is not currently available online. Please consult with Special Collections staff to request access. Note that Special Collections may not be able to provide required software or system specifications for all file formats.
    Other Finding Aids
    See the attached log file for a list of media copied. More detailed digital file lists are available upon request.
  - Wickedary Card File (Box 68, Box 69)
    This card file contains words that Daly defined in Wickedary. Cards include defenitions, research notes, and pointers to related words. Some addresses, postcards, and unrealted notes are mixed in.
  - Amazon Grace by Mary Daly, 2005 (Box 70)
  - Beyond God the Father by Mary Daly, 1973 (Box 70)
  - The Curch and the Second Sex by Mary Daly, 1968 (Box 70)
  - CMSW Annual Assembly Proceedings, including a paper presented by Daly, 1968 (Box 70)
  - Pure Lust by Mary Daly, 1984 (Box 70)
  - Gyn/Ecology by Mary Daly, 1990 (Box 70)
  - Outercourse by Mary Daly, 1993 (Box 70)
  - Quintessence by Mary Daly, 1998 (Box 70)
  - Webster's First Intergalactic Wickedary of the English Language by Mary Daly, 1985 (Box 70)
  - La Chiesa e il Secondo Sesso (The Church and the Second Sex), 1982 (Box 70)
  - Kirche Frau und Sexus (The Church and the Second Sex), 1970 (Box 70)
  - Gyn/Okologie (Gyn/Ecology), 1981 (Box 70)
  - Vecchi e Nuovi Dei with a chapter by Mary Daly, 1976 (Box 70)
  - Utopos. Kein Ort. Mary Daly's Patriarchatskritik und feministische Politik with chapters by Mary Daly, 1988 (Box 70)
  - Beyond God the Father in Korean, 1996 (Box 70)
  - The Church and the Second Sex in Japanese, 1982 (Box 70)
  - Quintessenza (Quintessence), 2005 (Box 70)
  - Jenseits von Gottvater (Beyond God the Father), 1980 (Box 70)
  - The Church and the Second Sex in Korean, 1994 (Box 70)
  - Al di la di Dio Padre (Beyond God the Father), 1990 (Box 70)
  - Auswarts Reisen (Outercourse), 1994 (Box 70)
  - Voorbij God de Vader (Beyond God the Father), 1983 (Box 70)
  - Reine Lust (Pure Lust), 1986 (Box 70)
  - Womanspirit Rising with chapter by Daly, 1979 (Box 70)
  - Controversial Conversations with Catholics with chapter by Daly, 1969 (Box 70)
  - Demands for Christian Renewal with chapter by Daly, 1968 (Box 70)
  - Sexist Religion and Women in the Church with chapter by Daly, 1974 (Box 70)
  - Religion for a New Generation with chapter by Daly, 1973 (Box 70)
  - We Won't Keep Silence Any Longer! with chapter by Daly (Box 70)
  - For Lesbians Only with chapter by Daly, 1988 (Box 70)
  - Wee Girls with chapter by Daly, 1996 (Box 70)
  - The Thomist with a book review by Daly, 1959 (Box 70)
  - Wanderlust/Wonderlust and The Qualitative Leap Beyond Patriarchal Religion by Mary Daly, 2002 (Box 71)
  - The Problem of Speculative Theology by Mary Daly, 1963 (Box 71)
  - The Mimetic Principle in the Literary Theory of John Crowe Ransom by Mary Daly, 1952 (Box 71)
  - Religious Education with an article by Mary Daly, 1972 (Box 71)
  - Women and Education with an article by Mary Daly, 1972 (Box 71)
  - The New Day with an chapter by Mary Daly, 1968 (Box 71)
  - The Problem of Speculative Theology by Mary Daly, 1965 (Box 71)
  - Natural Knowledge of God in the Philosophy of Jacques Maritain by Mary Daly, 1966 (Box 71)
  - Notes pour une ontologie du feminisme radical by Mary Daly, 1982 (Box 71)
  - Trivia with an article by Mary Daly, 1983 (Box 71)
  - Spiritual Life with an article by Mary Daly, 1959 (Box 71)
  - ARC with an article by Mary Daly, 2002 (Box 71)
  - AAR Women and Religion Proceedings with an article by Mary Daly, 1972 (Box 71)
  - The Thomist with a book review by Mary Daly, 1959 (Box 71)
  - AAR Women and Religion Proceedings with an article by Mary Daly, 1973 (Box 71)
  - Woman, Church and State with a foreword by Mary Daly, 1980 (Box 71)
  - The Thomist with an article by Mary Daly, 1965 (Box 71)
  - Feminist Studies with an article by Mary Daly, 1978 (Box 71)
  - Andover Newton Quarterly with an article by Mary Daly, 1972 (Box 71)
  - Philosophy for a New Generation with a chapter by Mary Daly, 1977 (Box 71)
  - Wickedary Poster (Box 73)
  - Floppy disk of Amazon Grace, 2003-07-29-2003-10-31; 2 items (2 floppy disks) (Box 74)
  - Floppy disk of Mary Daly's review of "Traveller in Space" by June Campbell, 1996-09-14; 1 items (1 floppy disk) (Box 74)
  - Floppy disk of Quintessence, 1994-12-31; 1 items (1 floppy disk) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly - Gyn/Ecology - Berkeley, CA, 1980 (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly Kellum lecture - Series on feminist thought, KPFA - Pure Lust, 2 items (2 audiocassettes) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly's Gyn/Ecology, station KPFA, 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of introduction for Pure Lust and lecture, 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly lecture on Pure Lust in Nova Scotia, 1984; 2 items (2 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly lecture on Pure Lust, 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly lecture on Wit and Wickedary at the London Lesbian Archive, 1988-04-21; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Gyn Ecology Cover (Box 73)
  - Pure Lust Cover (Box 73)
  - Outercourse Cover (Box 73)
  - Reine Lust Poster, 1986 (Box 73)
  - Prints (for Wickendary?) (Box 73)
  - Frauenoffensive Posters (Box 73)
  - Siehe, ich schaffe Neues (See, I have made new: Upheavals in women in Protestantism. Catholicism, Judaism - contains essay by Daly, 1998 (Box 71)
  - Del Cielo a la Tierra (From the Sky to the Earth: An Anthology of Feminist Theology) - includes translated essay of Daly's on contradictions in Christianity, 1994 (Box 71)
  - Vlasta (French feminist mag) - interview w Daly, translation of "Notes for an ontology of radical feminism" (Box 71)
  - Courage (German women's mag) No. 12, contains Daly article on spiritual politics, 1982 (Box 71)
  - Untitled Feminist Reader, contains essay by Daly on "The Spiritual Dimension of Women's Liberation", 1971 (Box 71)
  - The Second Wave Vol. 3 No. 1 - contains essay by Daly on Spiritual Revolution, 1973 (Box 71)
  - Quintessence Posters, 2000 (Folder 75)
- SERIES III. Correspondence, 1960-2013; 10.833 linear feet (14 containers)
  This series contains both personal and professional correspondence to and from Mary Daly, as well as fan mail. Correspondence is with students, colleagues, lawyers, publishers, and friends. Files also contain non-correspondence materials by and about people, including writings, theses, articles, and newspaper clippings. Some files contain no correspondence, just materials relating to the person listed- a name listed is not a guarantee Daly maintained correspondence with that person. There are also organizational and academic newsletters and ephemera as well as subject files interspersed in the series.
  - Kirsten Grimstad (Box 46)
  - Sally Hacker (Box 46)
  - Jane Caputi (Box 46)
  - Denise Connors (Box 46)
  - Elizabeth Gould Davis (Box 46)
  - de Beauvoir (Box 46)
  - Barbara Deming (Box 46)
  - Andrea Dworkin (Box 46)
  - Ecology (Box 46)
  - Eunuchism (Box 46)
  - Sarah Hoagland (Box 46)
  - Sociology of Literature (Box 46)
  - Kady (Box 46)
  - Billie Jean King (Box 46)
  - Elisabeth Kubler-Ross (Box 46)
  - Judith Laws -Tokenism (Box 46)
  - Language (Box 46)
  - Lesbian (Box 46)
  - Herbert Marcuse (Box 46)
  - Ellie McLaughlin (Box 46)
  - Nelle Morton (Box 46)
  - Julia Penelope (Box 46)
  - Psychosurgery (Box 46)
  - Janice Raymond (Box 46)
  - Julia Penelope (Box 46)
  - Joan Peters (Box 46)
  - Kenneth Pitchford (Box 46)
  - Denise Rauk (Box 46)
  - Janice Raymond (Box 46)
  - Beate Riesterer (Box 46)
  - Nancy Rosen (Box 46)
  - Mary Raffini (Box 46)
  - Joanna Russ (Box 46)
  - Susan Saxe (Box 46)
  - Martinnotte Schaer (Box 46)
  - Barbara Seaman (Box 46)
  - Mary Lou Shields (Box 46)
  - Julia Stanley (Box 46)
  - Sandra Stanley (Box 46)
  - Students (Box 46)
  - Thomas Szasz (Box 46)
  - St. Joan's Alliance United States Bulletin (Box 46)
  - Newsletters-Spokeswoman, June 1970 - June 1972 (Box 46)
  - Newsletters-Spokeswoman, July 1972 - October 1977 (Box 47)
  - NOW (Box 47)
  - Matrices (Lesbian feminist research newsletter) (Box 47)
  - Peggy Allegro (Box 47)
  - Artemis March (Box 47)
  - Jessie Bernard (Box 47)
  - Nicole Brossard (Box 47)
  - Chardin, Chastete, M. Daly (Box 47)
  - Lee Ann Hall (Box 47)
  - Pat Harrison (Box 47)
  - Sarah Hoagland (Box 47)
  - Beth Hodges (Box 47)
  - Peggy Holland (Box 47)
  - Mary Howell (Box 47)
  - Pat Hynes (Box 47)
  - Michelle Cliff (Box 47)
  - Denise Connors (Box 47)
  - Joan Aalfs (Box 47)